<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<!-- generator="Movable Type/2.63" -->
<rss version="0.91">
  <channel>
    <title>Kate&apos;s Page</title>
    <link>http://www.lakemonsterculture.com/kate/</link>
    <description>My Watson Fellowship 2003-2004</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster></webMaster>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2004 02:16:03 -0500</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Quarterly Report II</title>
      <link>http://www.lakemonsterculture.com/kate/archives/001151.html</link>
      <description>1/14/04 The searing Athenian sun and blue skies gave way to a much more tranquil autumn that carried the scents of earth softened by Mediterranean rain. The dry dust and high midday sun turned to gentle clouds and all the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarterly Report I</title>
      <link>http://www.lakemonsterculture.com/kate/archives/001152.html</link>
      <description>In the past, I have allowed my own romantic ideals, derived primarily from art and literature, dictate my expectations when dreaming out a train window. Of course, the machinations of my mind formed a London of Dickensian fog and umbrellas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>II.</title>
      <link>http://www.lakemonsterculture.com/kate/archives/000868.html</link>
      <description>Further Illuminated: The Buddhist and Christian illuminated manuscript tradition: Greece, Russia, India, Tibet During our period at the abbey his hands were always covered with the dust of books, the gold of still-fresh illumination, or with yellowish substances he touched...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I.</title>
      <link>http://www.lakemonsterculture.com/kate/archives/000867.html</link>
      <description>Further Illuminated: The Buddhist and Christian illuminated manuscript tradition: Greece, Russia, India, Tibet I propose a year abroad devoted to the study (including learning the production techniques) of illuminated manuscripts of the Christian and Buddhist traditions in Greece, Russia, India,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i.</title>
      <link>http://www.lakemonsterculture.com/kate/archives/000839.html</link>
      <description>Albatross Snake Pig Cow Moo Albatross Snake Pig Cow Moo Albatross Snake Pig Cow Moo Albatross Snake Pig Cow Moo Albatross Snake Pig Cow Moo Albatross Snake Pig Cow Moo Albatross Snake Pig Cow Moo Albatross Snake Pig Cow Moo...</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>